<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IKIGAI app</string>
    <string name="button_set_color">Set Color</string>
    <string name="button_set_line_width">Set Line Width</string>
    <string name="button_erase">Erase Image</string>
    <string name="label_red">Red</string>
    <string name="label_green">Green</string>
    <string name="label_blue">Blue</string>
    <string name="line_imageview_description">This displays the line thickness</string>
    <string name="message_error_saving">There was an error saving the image</string>
    <string name="message_erase">Erase the drawing?</string>
    <string name="message_saved">Your saved painting can be viewed in the Photos app by selecting Device Folders from that app\\’s menu</string>
    <string name="message_error_printing">Your device does not support printing</string>
    <string name="permission_explanation">To save an image, the app requires permission to write to external storage</string>
    <string name="title_color_dialog">Choose Color</string>
    <string name="title_line_width_dialog">Choose Line Width</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to ikigai</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="sob_iki">" The Ikigai App presents the user with a simple and quick way to get their Ikigai."</string>
    <string name="sig_ikigai">Ikigai is a Japanese word meaning something close to \"reason to live\". Usually a figure is made up of four circles that have all the possibilities of intersections between them</string>
    <string name="pay">Pay</string>
    <string name="o_ikigai_app">The Ikigai app</string>
    <string name="need">Need</string>
    <string name="mas_o_que_o_ikigai">"But what is Ikigai? "</string>
    <string name="man_mon">Mount IKIGAI manually</string>
    <string name="love">Love</string>
    <string name="initial_help">By clicking the start button you will have two options to mount your ikigai. Auto-Mount: Where the app itself creates the 4 circles for you. Manually Mount: Where you can manually enter each circle by choosing the color for each one. Let\'s start?</string>
    <string name="initial_msg">" Discover now your IKIGAI!"</string>
    <string name="good">Good</string>
    <string name="exp_ikigai">"In order to get your Ikigai, one begins by drawing the four circles. Once drawn, you have to fill in the fields of each circle that has no intersection with the others. The filling should look like this: - What do you love? \"What does the world need?\" \"What can you get paid for?\" \"What are you good at?\" Once this is done, the person discovers what they are: - their mission - their vocation - their profession - their passion. It is also up to the individual to fill in these four fields. Note that the intersections of 3 circles represent motives of dissatisfaction in life that people may have. In order to find fullness, they must consider the missing circle, giving rise to their Ikigai. "</string>
    <string name="entendi">Got it!</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="como_gostaria">" How would you like to set up your IKIGAI?"</string>
    <string name="choose_circle">Choose the Circle:</string>
    <string name="aut_mon">Auto mount</string>
    <string name="alert_select">You must select an option to continue.</string>
    <string name="about">About the App</string>
    <string name="label_alpha">Alpha</string>
    <string name="EN">EN</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="print">Print</string>
    <string name="desenhar_circulo">Draw Circle</string>
    <string name="color">Colors</string>
    <string name="erase">Erase</string>
    <string name="tamanho_linha">Line Size</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="quiser_apagar">" When including all circles, your ikigai should look similar to the one above. If you do not like the color, you can delete and redo it as many times as you like by clicking the delete option in the side menu of the application."</string>
    <string name="mon_ikig">Before selecting the color, you must choose a circle. You should only perform this procedure once for each circle, but all circles must be designed to validate Ikigai.</string>
    <string name="how_ikigai">How to mount your Ikigai?</string>
    <string name="cor_circulo">" When you choose the color and circle, it will appear on the screen similar to this."</string>
    <string name="click_ikigai">" Clicking on the circles icon in the application's activity bar will open a menu with color options to color your circle."</string>
    <string name="alterar_ikigai">" You can change the color using the bars and you can see a preview of the color before selecting."</string>
</resources>